LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Take a look at this photo.
The girl in the middle.
I've seen her somewhere...
She isn't the girl from Tokura Electronics, is she?
Indeed.
The Kokoku Brigade, a sect of the Human
Emancipation Front, kidnapped her 16 years ago.
She is Eka, the Tokura Electronics
president's only daughter.
Nice expression.
It was a time when people didn't get a cyberbrain as casually as they do now.
This kid was given a cyberbrain to advertise
her father's company's latest product.
But as a result, she caught their eye
and was kidnapped...
Yes, I remember it well.
Somehow, I think this is our business.
I remember...
That case was never solved.
They didn't find her even though they raided
many hideouts and asked a lot of questions.
So, this picture was taken when she was kidnapped?
No, that's from two days ago.
They are at a radioactive decontamination plant
200 nautical miles off the shores of Okinawa.
A member of the Japanese Coast
Guard SST took this picture.
Two days ago?
That means this isn't really her.
I wouldn't necessarily say that.
The Japanese Coast Guard sent advance troops
to the plant for a secret investigation...
when they received information about
the Brigade landing at the plant.
They just happened to find her there.
This DNA data came with the report.
We don't know how the SST got this data, but it
is an exact match with her past medical records.
This is the last thing we heard from the
troops, we lost contact with all four of them.
That's that.
We will see what is going on there.
UNEQUAL
TERRORIST
Batou, how is it?
No one's here.
There's no trace of anyone entering.
Even the Brigade did not come
down to the lowest level.
It's me.
Are you in?
Yeah, the deck was secured.
The security system is doing better than expected, even
though it has been left unattended for more than 10 years.
It's attached to the ship quite well.
There are no problems.
Okay.
Ishikawa, is there any movement above the plant?
It's quitE calm, just right for night fishing.
There is one GPS transmission that
we can confirm is from an SST member.
It's possible that he will come out of
the plant on his own when he sees us.
It only takes you two minutes to land, so standby.
Roger.
Like he said.
What do you say we take a leisurely
tourist flight while we wait.
Major, it's a dead end.
I can see that.
Ahh... umm... if you permit,
I can destroy the barricade...
No.
Act like an adult when we're
closing in on the target.
Yes ma'am.
it'll be a pain in the butt,
but we'll have to find another way in.
There must be something going on up
ahead, since there's a barricade here.
You don't plan on going that way, do you?
I hope this isn't a dead end.
Major...
I've been thinking...
aren't we walking into the
Brigade's trap by doing this?
Even though we can confirm where the survivors
are, it's suspicious that there's no response.
You think all the troops were wiped out?
I'm not saying that.
You're thinking it too, right, Major?
She can't be the real thing.
Then what is she?
Well, a cyborg is the first
thing that came to my mind.
Did you forget that they are a sect
of the Human Emancipation Front?
They are a group that opposes
cyborgs and cyberbrains,
I don't think that's it.
In addition, the DNA test results
from the SST's last report,
how do you explain them?
Don't you think that the Brigade would
have preserved blood and cell samples?
They could make a clone from that.
What for?
Umm.
For example, trying to get Tokura's inheritance?
There isn't any evidence to
contradict the clone theory right now,
but there's no benefit to a clone suddenly appearing
as she did 16 years ago, other than to appeal to emotions.
Clones can't legally inherit anything either...
Even though there are inconsistencies,
they must have a reason for it.
Don't you want to see what is
going on with your own two eyes?
We'll investigate it once we
rescue the real person, right?
Togusa-kun just can't stop murmuring can he?
Thank's for waiting.
No matter how you look at it,
cyborg food just seems tasteless.
Huh?
Nonsense, want to try?
Well, we can't do anything
until the next GPS transmission.
Take it easy.
Think about this, the sea surrounds it.
They could be self-sufficient if they wanted to.
In addition to the ocean-lovers, this seems
like an important trading place, doesn't it?
But, but, this situation is
more than just that data!
We don't even know how the terrorists go in.
The neighbouring countries might become hysterical.
Ah, waaiit!
Oh! Mister, nice robot you have there.
How about it?
I'll trade this thinking engine for that robot.
Really? Show me, show me!
No way, let's go.
All right, I'll even throw in a Logical
Operation Device that was made in Taiwan!
This is a very valuable antique!
Ah, Batou-San, SST member Sakakihara's
GPS transmission has been confirmed.
Really?
It is moving upwards this time.
I sure wish they'd just stay put.
It doesn't matter if it's friend or foe!
You're SST's Sakakihara, right?
Don't worry, help's here.
Hey!
Please delete it...
Ah, what's with you?
It's okay now.
I beg you... delete it.
I'm counting on you.
WAH! Be gone!
Hang in there!
What's there?
Hey!
Hey, can you understand me?
What happened to the other three?
Th-They were killed...
If she became a leader...
What did you say?
Delete it...
I beg you.
Hey, what do you mean by leader?
She was alive... so why did such a...
Life is too cruel...
Did he connect? To her...
The girl...
This is...
I see.
We're definitely narrowing it
down and getting closer to her.
Togusa-kun, you're rather nervous, aren't you?
This is no time to be joking!
Togusa, how is it over there?
No one's here.
The place in the photo is
right above here, isn't it?
There aren't any other control
rooms in this plant either...
Police.
Where is Eka Tokura right now?
This bastard is underestimating me!
Major, let me try.
You know about the "dentist" torture, don't you?
But I bet you've never felt it yourself.
Tachikoma, make sure no one comes in here.
Roger!
Enough already!
Do you know what this is?
You've done the same thing over and over again!
When will you be satisfied?
I have no patience anymore!
Major, it's me.
We've rescued the SST survivor.
He's in good health, but his cyberbrain
was slightly damaged by a virus.
I've tried radio transmission,
but he couldn't respond.
Got it.
Go wait at the heliport.
I'll take care of things here.
Hold on.
There's something you should know.
What?
That girl has something to do
with Sakakihara going insane.
He couldn't say it directly, but it seems like
that girl is becoming the leader of the Brigade.
I don't think you would
lose in a cyberbrain fight,
but at least be careful when
you connect to that girl.
From now on, you cannot leave
my side without my permission.
Why can't you understand that?
Do you really want to leave me alone that much?
You're always...
Acting like a princess, aren't you?
Or like a cliched revolutionary.
Who's there?
The police.
Put your hands up.
Hurry up, I won't warn you again.
Do you think you'll be able to walk
out of here alive if you do this?
Major, what's wrong?
It's not...
that kid.
Major, a band of armed soldiers are closing in.
Major.
Tachikoma, what's the situation?
They have infiltrated!
It seems like they're ambushing
Batou-San from behind.
Tachikoma, come here, quickly.
We have our objective.
Retreat.
Roger!
Huh?
It's started, hasn't it?
All right, take her down.
Shit, he's in the way.
Tachikoma, take him in.
Roger!
Huh?
What?
Now we're the targets.
They're fucking using their
comrades bodies as shields!
I can't cut it.
Tachikoma, aim at the wires!
Roger!
High velocity ammo, huh?
You used something that powerful.
Wah! Fight!
Geez, they're not bad.
They're completely unafraid of
death despite not being cyborgs!
Where's Batou?
Rescuing the female gorilla?
How unnecessary.
Wait, don't attack, it's me.
Why did you come?
Why? To help you of course.
Eh?
Wait, where's the girl?
In the Tachikoma, because she's being annoying.
Ah...
What's with that old woman?
Bring her along.
Huh?
You'd better explain later.
You go first, Togusa.
I'll buy us some time.
How's that?
You fool!
Did you forget that someone's in your pod!
But, but, I want to fight more!
Anti-tank missiles!
Let's run away!
Don't get shot!
Leave it to me
Head for the control tower.
Tachikoma, go first!
Roger!
All right, go!
Batou.
Huh?
Don't touch my mom with your dirty hands!
M-mom?
Let me go!
Such an unmanageable girl.
I said let me go!
You! Don't touch my mother!
Let me go, you...!
Wow, that's the place from the rumours, isn't it?
Eh? Where, where?
Tell me!
She's really younger than I am.
The media will be in an uproar.
Yeah.
Those SST people realised, just as the Major did,
that the old lady was the real Tokura
Eka, not the girl.
When they figured that out,
they tried directly connecting to her,
and they connected to her cyberbrain.
"Delete it", huh?
At first, I didn't know what that meant.
It meant, "delete my memories", didn't it?
Sixteen years after being kidnapped,
a ten year old girl has aged
enough to look like an old woman.
I don't want to even imagine
what happened during that time.
The remaining question is why Eka's daughter
ended up in a position to lead those guys...
You want to find out?
Connect to her.
Nah, I'll pass.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up